import 'package:quiz_app_tutorial/models/question.dart';
// import 'package:appliccation/';

 const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question: '1.What is the meaning of HTML?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Hyper Text Markup Language',
      'b) Hyper markup',
      'c) Hyper text makrkup',
      'd) None of the above',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. Which of these is used for styling web pages?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Css',
      'b) Html',
      'c) Java',
      'd) None of the above',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. What is the extension of a JavaScript file',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) .jss',
      'b) .js',
      'c) .jsx',
      'd) .jpx',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. Which of the following is a loca storage',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) PHP',
      'b) HTML',
      'c) Css',
      'd) javascript',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. Which of the following is used for web dynamism',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Html',
      'b) Css',
      'c) JavaScript',
      'd)None of the above',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '6.Which of the following is not used for styling web pages',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Css',
      'b) Js',
      'c) Php',
      'd) C++',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. _What is the full meaning of Css',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Cascading syle sheet',
      'b) Cascaded style',
      'c) cast style sheet',
      'd) cast sheet',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. Which of the followig is not a programming language?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) C',
      'b) Css',
      'c) Javascript',
      "d) python",
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '9.The language used for algorithms similar to English is?.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Css',
      'b) C',
      'c) html',
      'd) Pseudo code',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '10. TWhich of the foolowing uses Dart?.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Js',
      'b) Css',
      'c) Flutter',
      'd) Angular',
    ],
  ),
];
